Finding Aid for the Honey Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series VI: Speeches
  - Series VI: Speeches, 1979-1983
    - Foster Care-Memphis Junior League, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - NASW-UTCHS Child Development, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Accord, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Adolescent Wellness-Akins, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - First Lady – Speeches, 1983-1988
    - Blankenship-Baird, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Baird, 1983 (1 of 2) (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Baird, 1983 (2 of 2) (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Baird-Brandt, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Brown-Coyne, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Cox-Chivers, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Edwards-Locke, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - McKnight-Private Sector, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Shayne-Socha, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee Public Health-Word, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Baird-Handicapped Child, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Harpeth Hall-Healthy Children, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Leadership Memphis-Teen Pregnancy, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Teen Pregnancy-Tennessee’s Most Precious Resources, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Young Children’s Education – circa, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Healthy Children, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Cable, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - General, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Speech Materials, 1980-1988 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Development of Goals and Priorities, or Gaining Control of My Life, undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Series VII: Calendars, Schedules, and Appointment Books
  - First Lady – Calendars, Schedules, and Appointment Books, 1978-1981
    - Calendar, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Calendar, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Calendar, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Book, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Calendar, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - First Lady – Task Force on Mental Retardation Prevention, 1982-1985
    - Calendar, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Calendar, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Calendar, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Calendar, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - First Lady – Calendars, Schedules, and Appointment Books, 1986-1989
    - Calendar, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Calendar, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Calendar, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Calendar, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - First Lady – Calendars, Schedules, and Appointment Books, 1978-1985
    - Schedules, 1978 January-June (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Schedules, 1978 January-September (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Schedules, 1978 January-October (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Schedules, 1978 February (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Schedules, 1978 February-April (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Schedules, 1978 February-June (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Schedules, 1978 April (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Schedules, 1978 May-July (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Schedules, 1978 May-September (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Schedules, 1978 June-July (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Schedules, 1978 July (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Schedules, 1978 August (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Schedules, 1978 September (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Schedules, 1978 October (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Schedules, 1978 October (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Schedules, 1978 October 23 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Schedules, 1978 October-November (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Schedules, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Schedules, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Series VIII: Journals and Travel Documents
  - First Lady – Journals and Travel Documents, 1980-1987
    - Journal, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Journal, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Journal, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Journal, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Journal, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Journal, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - First Lady – Journals and Travel Documents, 1982-1985
    - “Outward Bound” Course Diary – circa, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Trip Journal – circa, 1985 September-October (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Official Trips, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Official Trips, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Travel – Bauch-Crowell, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Travel – Carter-Davidson, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Travel – Davidson-Debby, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Travel – Ellis-Hudson, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Travel – Hyde-Fain, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Travel – Grand Canyon, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Travel – Fishman-Kruidenier, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Travel – Koala Adolescent Center, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Travel – Lewis-Munsey, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Travel – PBS Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Travel – Rhem-Ridley, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Travel – Sivley-Smith, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Travel – Spencer-Turner, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Travel – Waller-Williams, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Travel – Wood, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 19)